Do you want to use it?
What do you think?
Is it here?
You know, it's kind of laggy in here.
It's still laggy.
You know, I'm wondering if anyone looking back at the archives would be interested in stretching it out here.
Do you want to take a look at it?
Would you look at it?
I know you can hear me.
Do you think they can hear you?
Can you hear me? Guys.
Oh, here they are.
I know you can hear me.
Can you hear me?
Good. So, once again, good evening, everyone.
We went to the bartenders' time!
It's been a while since we've seen each other.
I'm Kiina from Spring. Pleased to meet you.
I am Miyu Yanagi. Nice to meet you.
I am Rika Koeda. Pleased to meet you.
I am Kana Sada. Pleased to meet you.
I am Riroa Aoi. Pleased to meet you.
I am Mai Kiya. Nice to meet you.
So, it's been a little while since I've done a live broadcast on YouTube,
We decided to do this live broadcast on short notice, and it was announced yesterday as an emergency live broadcast,
We will continue to hold various live performances and events in the future,
We are going to hold a lot of live concerts and events in the future, so we thought it would be good for us to organize them, or rather, we think there are some things we don't understand,
So we have decided to distribute it.
Thank you very much.
So, before I release more information,
I would like to make a report to all of you.
There is something that is not right,
Miyu Yanagi, who is a member of our group,
I'm sorry to have to tell you this, but a change has occurred.
A pretty big change.
What is it? What is this?
Do you guys understand?
I'm not tall enough anymore.
That's for sure.
It's my feet getting bigger.
Ah.
Indeed. It also became taller.
Ah, I see.
Yes, I see. The skin has become moist.
Strong legs.
I'm fine.
Can you tell from this distance?
But if you can't tell, I'm sorry, but you're disqualified.
That's right.
If you don't recognize this,
The comment section is moving very fast.
It's moving.
No one thinks to look at the comments.
It's moving pretty fast.
I don't think they'll get through.
What do you think? What do you think?
They seem to have noticed.
Did we have a visual explosion?
Ah.
Always.
That's right.
I've gone gal.
You're in high school, right?
I see. It's a thing, isn't it?
BB-san spachar at this timing.
Thank you.
I should write an answer or something.
Good evening.
Thank you very much.
First of all, my hair grew back.
It's not in.
It's in there, in case you were wondering.
May I ask Miyu to give the correct answer?
Yes. I, Mie Yanagi, have made bangs this time.
This time.
That's good.
You all look cute.
Why did you suddenly want to make them?
I've always wanted to make them.
I had the desire to make it.
I just didn't have the courage.
Now that I'm in high school and my spring tour is over, I thought I'd wear it.
I thought I would wear it.
It's cute.
I think you all now have a reason to come see me again.
I hope you will all come to see Mie Yanagi.
I'm glad. It's not a bad change.
I'm glad to see her.
So, I don't mean to be too forward, but....
Before we talk about the 8th anniversary and the request live, we haven't had a chance to look back on the spring tour.
That's for sure.
This should not happen.
It is not allowed.
I think we have been looking back on the tour individually, through the distribution and so on, but I think we should look back on it together.
I would like to look back together.
You mean about three weeks ago, right?
That's right.
A lot.
Almost a month.Almost a month.
That's not good.
We started on April 1 in Fukuoka and finished on Saturday, May 13 in Shinjuku, Tokyo.
How was everyone?
What do you think?
It was extremely difficult.
I wonder why.
Like Chiko.
Yes, like Chiko.
You're waving your hands.
It's more than I expected,
It was more like a puff.
It was like a hmmm.
Everyone was.
Certainly, certainly.
It depends on who's easier to talk to.
Okay, Amiyu.
I'm cutting my bangs.
Let's go.
Let's go this time,
I'm going to tour around Fukuoka City,
I also had the opportunity to visit Taiwan,
It was a tour outside of Japan,
That's right.
I met many people in each place,
I was able to meet many people in each place,
At the last show in Shinjuku
I fell in love with them at the last show in Shinjuku,
It was a new tour for me.
It was indeed a new tour for me.
First of all, Taiwan,
I want to include Taiwan in the tour.
We were so excited.
It was great,
There was a lot of directing this time, too.
We were also very involved in the production of the show,
Taiwan, you know,
When it comes to overseas performances
It's different,
There were some difficulties,
I think we were able to deliver a live show only in Taiwan.
I think we were able to deliver a live performance
I think we were able to deliver a live performance that was only possible in Taiwan,
The members of the group often say
In Osaka on April 30,
I was able to get unscrewed without any problems,
That's right.
It was a time when things got a little crazy.
This is it.
What?
What is it?
It's like this, it's like...
What was it?
It's unscrewed.
I didn't understand.
I'm sorry.
Ai-chan said that too, right?
You did say that, didn't you?
We were looking back the other day at another place.
When everyone was saying that to each other,
It was fun, and Ata Sawakawa said it too.
But, you know,
Think about it. From Fukuoka.
Are you doing Taiwan?
And then Osaka,
Things definitely got a little crazy.
We did. You went crazy.
What?
I don't remember.
I think I might have been saying
I might have said so from the beginning.
Ai-chan pulled me along.
She pulled me along.
Is there something wrong? It's like this place is unscrewed.
That's what I mean.
Who is it?
Are you talking about the physical? Now.
Not a pinpoint.
I thought it might be here.
I thought maybe this was it.
Yeah, it's here. There is.
It's been a while since I've done a live YouTube feed.
Like falling into a bit of a panic.
It was like this.
Well, in Osaka.
Kansai dialect and all.
Our original
Kansai dialect and so on.
I was able to be more frank.
That's the kind of thing
It was like a fairy tale.
Until Taiwan, we had been proper.
I was being proper. Until the end.
More than that, until Taiwan.
I was doing fine.
But, you know, I was suspicious. Ai-chan in Taiwan.
I called her "Papillo" under the influence.
Is it strange if I call her Papilo? I thought it was a little strange.
I think she was shining.I think the feeling was, you know, shining.
I think it was a brilliant day.
I went to Osaka with a bang.
I went from Osaka to Sapporo on May 6, and then to Sapporo on May 13.
Sapporo on May 6 and Shinjuku on May 13.
Shinjuku on May 13th were also quite
I think they were quite open and frank live shows.
I think so.
At the end of the show, we had an exposure contest.
We became the MC team.
It started, didn't it?
No, it did. So I was.
I was wrong at first.
I was the one who was
exposed that I was wrong. That's why I want you all
Because it's the final leg of the tour
I forgive you. That's what I meant.
I also made a mistake here.
I thought, "I made a mistake here, too.
I thought you wanted me to say it.
Me too. I don't want you to say anything at all.
I don't want you to write anything.
All of us.
Wai-wai-wai.
But that's something that only happens on tour.
I guess.
It's not so bad. It's not so much for a one-time
I don't think you can go that far in a one-time
I don't think I would go that far.
But that too.
Nine shows in five locations. So, it was a lot of exposure for everyone.
There were a lot of them.
But I think Ayanan is having a lot of fun, too,
I think we can build on this, or rather, play with it,
That's right.
Aya-chan was hitting the cat.
You know, I was surprised.
I was so surprised.
She didn't recognize it as a cat,
I don't know, I don't know,
She was too excited,
I mean, he was just too excited about the family,
Like, "Boo.
I don't remember Boh being a long cat. I guess so.
Yes, he was.
And then he said, "Well, we have a family, so let's fight.
I don't know..,
Did you notice them during the show? The members?
Yes, I did.
I saw them.
They were like this, you know, right there.
That's when I noticed.
Once I looked at Mie-chan,
I said, "It's okay.
I controlled it without looking at her.
The stimulation was coming out.
It was too strong.
It's quite pitiful how they treat cats, isn't it?
I was being pushed around.
I was swinging it around.
There was a scene where a big crocodile and a bear were holding the cat in the stuffed animal house,
That was a lot of work, wasn't it?
It was big.
It was a lot of work, so I was happy to see them.
I was happy when they were tiny.
Because I could do it.
It was free.
Because you could do what you wanted.
That's true.
That was great.
Were you happy to hold the stuffed animals, Rina-chan?
I was so happy.
I heard that Rina was also a fan of pink bears,
I was so happy when I got it,
She was so happy when it came that she went to get it, saying "bear", and was a little scared.
Sakura also had only one performance with meat, right?
It was the last performance, and the audience wanted to have the meat, no matter what,
It's funny how they wanted us to have meat,
It was different every time.
Isn't that amazing?
Yes, it was.
Is there anything you don't have? On the contrary.
Rina has a lot.
Hearts, too.
Riko has a lot of hearts.
That's true.
When I went to get hearts, the staff would say, "Oh, Riko, you have a lot of hearts,
hearts and a big bear or a big crocodile,
So I guess I would say hearts.
You have to pick it out yourself.
That's right.
Only two.
Because he has two hands, he only has two pieces,
When one of them is taken away, another one is added.
During the process, I was choosing the mouth that Kido liked, right?
Chosen.
I was doing the picking and choosing.
On the good side, you know, he gave me a present when I went.
Yes, that's right.Yes.
But it's hard to say,
There was an alligator. A big alligator.
It had a tail. It was quite a tragedy.
We stepped on it.
It was terrible, wasn't it?
It was a little long, wasn't it?
From the tail.
Something was coming out.
That was also a happening.
I'm sure everyone is fine now that they don't have to see it anymore.
It was fun.
There were costumes with lasers and such,
And the costume changes, too,
That was cool too.
It was cool.
I touched it a few times.
Didn't you say it was hot?
It was hot.
It was a little hot.
You didn't touch it?
I didn't feel hot. Not really.
It's pretty strong, isn't it? I mean, it's got a strong sensitivity to lasers and stuff.
That's cool.
It's really cool.
I think everyone enjoyed the cool movie and communication.
And you did the voice-over until the end,
It was my first one-man show.
It was amazing. It was as I expected.
Even at the beginning.
Yes, it was. I heard your answer,
I thought, "Wow.
I thought, "Yes, that's right.
You were really into it.
You hadn't sent out a message for about three years.
And then all of a sudden, you just let it out.
Were you practicing?
Actually, I was practicing.
People say they don't practice because they are embarrassed.
Actually, I use it as a pillow or something.
Oh, I see.
I don't have a sound system.
So I was watching the video, and there were parts where the calls increased again between the first and second parts,
I was really happy.
I wonder if you are going to make more and more graphic bands with the fans after the show.
I'm looking forward to seeing more and more of the gatchiri graphic bands after the fans,
I am looking forward to it.
I'm very happy.
So, from here on out
I would like to announce Jappi's event and
I would like to start with the information meeting about Jappi's events and benefit meetings.
First one.
Tomorrow and the day after tomorrow, Friday, June 9th
at United Lab in Fukuoka, Japan.
I will be performing at Philosophy's Dance Ant
I will be performing at the Divan Live.
Please give me your best regards.
This way.
After the show, we will have a special event for a short time.
The benefit will be a group shot only,
You can choose your pose,
But since it's after the show, it's time for us to be Cinderella.
Yes, it's a bit cramped. It's a bit cramped, isn't it?
We don't have the time to be Cinderella all the time,
We can't be Cinderella all the time,
It's limited.
We have a limited time to be pretty.
We can't be cute.
I can't show it to you.
I can't see her anymore.
We've been working for 26 hours.
I'm sorry.
We have a lot of time, so the time is very short,
If you want to join us,
I hope to see you all by the end of the day,
I want you to think of a pose,
I would like you to participate in this event.
So if you all are skipping the meeting, skipping today and tomorrow,
If you all skip today and tomorrow, how many of you will not be able to take pictures?
Then how many of you will not be able to take pictures?
We won't be pretty.
So, let's do it while we still can,
Today.
I'll think about it and go to bed.
Otherwise, don't go to bed.
Really.
Think of it as a fest.
Think about it,
I hope you can join us.
I'm sure there will be more information about this later,
The first round of tickets will start at 16:30,
If you do not have a ticket, you will not be able to participate in the benefit,
If you do not have a ticket, you will not be able to participate in the special event,
Please get your tickets as soon as possible.
So, it has been about a year and a half since you and Hirona have played together?
Yes, I think so.
Like in April.
It's been a year.
It's been a year since we last played together,I guess it will be,
How do you think the concert will turn out? Rira-chan.
Yes, it's been a while.
It's been a while since we last met,
I think everyone's enjoyment will be doubled.
It's nice.
There are things that can only happen when you play opposite each other.
I knew it.
Oh?
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to the show,
I want to dance a lot. Together.
No, no, no.
We will have a gutsy set list,
We hope that Hirona's fans will also enjoy the show,
And of course, the members as well,
We hope you will enjoy the show, including Hirona's live performance,
I am sure that you will enjoy the show, including Hirona's live performance,
We are looking forward to seeing you there,
If you are still on the fence, please come and see us.
It's rare to see a live performance by a performer who has undergone a metamorphosis,
I'm not usually able to come on Saturdays and Sundays, but I'd like to come.
Yes, that's true.
Yes, that's true. I'll be waiting for you.
And the second thing.
This weekend, Sunday, June 11,
I will be performing on the Olive Stage at the Hiroshima Flower Festival.
Thank you very much.
That's nice.
I have performed on stage with ℃-ute before,
What year?
We were wearing our 3rd anniversary costumes.
Five years ago, I think.
Oh my god.
White mash.
Wow.
I'm looking forward to it.
There are two stages,
The first stage starts at 2:40 p.m. and the second stage starts at 5:10 p.m,
The second stage will start at 5:10 pm.
The first stage starts at 2:40pm and the second stage starts at 5:10pm,
If you are in the area, we would be very happy if you could come and play with Battery Girl.
Please come and join us.
Of course, we have the setlist for this stage as well.
Yes, we do.
What kind of show is it going to be? Keena-san.
Is it me?
But I'm sure the first-timers will be happy to see you.
Yes, it will be.
You can dance.
Yes, I can. Exactly.
Also, there are some songs where you can speak out a bit, aren't there?
Yes, for sure.
I think it will be fun. I think this show will be fun, too.
After all, it's a festival.
A flower festival.
Everyone was full of flowery feeling. I think everyone will be blooming on the day of the festival.
I think everyone will be in full bloom on the day of the festival,
I'm sure there will be flowers blooming around you on the day of the festival, so I'd be happy to see you there.
And we are going to have a special event at the Flower Festival too.
Thank goodness.
We will have a special benefit at the Flower Festival as well.
We will have more information about this later, so please wait for it.
The award session will be a random 4-shot event,
Three randomly selected members and one customer will be in 4 shots.
How nice. I'm surrounded.
That's nice.
It's good.
So, the benefit event will be held from 3:15 to 4:00 p.m., and from 5:45 to 6:30 p.m. in two parts,
5:45 p.m. to 6:30 p.m. There will be two sessions.
Each group will be randomly divided into A and B groups.
Does that mean I will be able to get with different members?
I guess so.
Well, you can come to all of them.
That's for sure.
You can get it.
We may have a tight time frame,
So please don't go to sleep thinking about it already from today.
If you don't go to bed early, you will look sad when we take your picture,
I'll pose quickly and get out of here.
Yes.
Yes. Please do that.
Details of the benefit will be posted on SNS and other places later,
Please check there.
And the third one.
Next week on Saturday, June 17.
We will be performing at the NHK festival.
Thank you very much.
Thank you every year.
From 18:00.
Won.
Difficult.
First time.
I will be performing at Woon.
Thank you for this is another show that I have been able to perform at every year.Thank you for this is another gig that I have performed at every year.
But it is always a dungeon before rap with Mr. Puri and his friends.
Freestyle dungeon.
Yes, because we did.
I would like to do that again someday.
I would like to do that again,
This is also a really warm venue for us.
I'd like to do that again someday.
So we would be very happy if you could come and see us.
We are not sure about the benefit event yet,
We are not sure about the benefit party yet, so I hope you will wait for it,
I hope you will wait for it.
Please come and visit us at the SNS Festival.
Please come to the SNS Festival.
And now, I am waiting for you.
On Saturday, July 8, we will be holding the Canal City Theater 2.8 Anniversary Live.
Congratulations!
It is the 8th anniversary.
Come on, it's our first time to be at the Canal City Theater,
This was originally a theater used by a theater company, wasn't it?
It was originally used by a theater company, but recently it has become a venue for live performances as well,
So I think it will be a highlight to see what kind of set will be used.
It's a bit different from a regular live house or a hall,
I think it might be a little different from a regular live house or a concert hall,
The audience was blue, wasn't it?
The audience was blue.
Yes, they were.
Yes, they certainly were.
The seats on the second floor are also quite easy to see,
Also, the people of Fukuoka are represented by Canal City.
Canal City.
The representative of the people of Fukuoka.
Everyone goes there. Canal City.
It's a place of hope.
So I really hope you will come to Canal City.
Live concerts.
You can spend your time doing various things.
You can have fun.
I hope that you will not have so much fun that you don't come to the live concerts.
I hope that will be the case.
And I'm sure you have a set list.
I'm sure there will be a setlist.
Almost.
You're doing it, aren't you?
No, it's amazing.
Amazing.
Isn't that unexpected?
It's unexpected, isn't it?
I said this, but isn't it unexpected to start?
It was unexpected.
That was aggressive.
You were aggressive.
I don't mean the start. I mean, I was pretty aggressive. Overall.
Yes, I agree.
It's definitely bad.
It's pretty bad.
I'm sorry, it's been a while since we've played.
We couldn't hold it in the beginning, so we stopped. It's possible.
It's not impossible.
We are going to rehearse, so I hope it won't come to that.
Why don't you all keep your strength up?
Even if you all lose it.
Yes, that's right.
If something like that happens in the second half.
There's a fluffy sheet.
It's so funny.
Don't look at it right away.
It's no good.
I wonder where they'll notice it.
Why?
I think so much.
Oh, no.
That's for sure.
I wonder if they'll notice. Soon.
But those who do will understand.
But I'm sure you'll see it later and think, "Oh, well?
It's fun.
I see.
You have an idea.
That's true.
But there are people who notice it the first time.
If I had to guess, I'd say so.
I'm really looking forward to it.
And the costumes are being finalized,
The members of the group have suggested some ideas for the costumes,
You are very particular about your costumes, aren't you?
Yes, it is.
What do you think? Aya.
Yes, I like it.
But..,
Japan.
Certainly certainly.
I kind of want to wear it in Paris.
Ah! But you know what I mean.
It's nice.
It sure is.
Sakura likes it a lot too.Sakura is also quite a favorite.
I thought it was so much.
It was my type of shape.
Oh no. It's nice.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's a little deep.
So that's what it is, really.
With Mr. and Ms.?
Really.
Even those in the back of the hall,
I also wanted people in the back to know who was who.
I put that in.
Yes, I did.
With a bang.
I didn't write names.
As expected.
When we all say it.
It's not Urarikoto.
I see.
What do you think?
I'm sure one of you won't say it.
Yes, there is.
Right?
Urariko, too.
Yes, there is.
I don't like it.
But it's a lot of fun.
It's fun.
It's going to be a live show.
I think it will be fun.
I'm sure it will be. I'm sure it will be.
The 6th anniversary will be a rather royal live concert.
That's right.
The 7th anniversary was a cool concert,
The 8th anniversary is already fun.
Looking for something new.
Let's have fun.
Let's be playful.
And we'll be doing the ad-libs that we've been polishing in the spring tour.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm sure there will be times when I'll use it.
I'm sure there will be some.
Also, you might want to buy some throat lozenges.
Yes, sir.
The set list is as follows,
Please look forward to it.
I heard that there are not many tickets left,
Oh, I hear it's going to be difficult.
I hear it's going to be hard to find tickets,
If you are not sure about it, please check tickets as soon as possible,
If you have any doubts, please check the tickets as soon as possible,
I hope you will join us to celebrate our 8th anniversary,
But here's the thing.
But here's something else.
There is something here that is not old at all.
Did you notice it?
I forgot about it,
This is it.
It's not something I've ever seen before.
I'm sure.
Yes, it is.
First time seeing it.
Ah.
The light.
What is this?
It's a penlight.
It's cute.
I've never seen it before.
Is this a product that will be released for the 8th anniversary?
Yes, it is.
Wow!
It's so cute.
It's so beautiful.
Beautiful.
The colors are amazing.
And the patterns on the spring tour t-shirts,
They are all sitting in color.
Sitting?
Really!
That's amazing.
It's so cute.
They're sitting in their colored clothes. We finally made it.
There it is. We were all together. All of us.
And we were all lined up like chon-chon-chon.
Amazing.
It's a very cute pattern. This one.
I found it first.
Really? You're fast.
It stopped disappearing.
I was messing around with glitter and it stopped disappearing,
The manager made it disappear.
Disappeared?
Huh!
I broke it. This one.
This one, the pink one.
Aaah!
I'm glad, I'm glad.
Thank you.Thank you.
I did it.
Good, good, good.
I don't know if there's anything to read, but I'm sure you guys have read the instructions.
Oh, it's so cute.
Can I get a closer look?
Yes. This way?
Yes, this way. This one.
There's a lot going on here, isn't there?
Then, please, let's have a look. Goods.
Goods are coming this way.
Please stop it.
It's dangerous.
It's a little dangerous.
Oh, you want to see it light up?
Oh, it doesn't glow anymore. Next time.
Oh, oh!
Panic?
It's flickering.
That's good. Can you guys see it?
Yeah, I see it.
What's that? What is it?
What is it?
Oh, my God!
I just realized that nearly 1,000 people have viewed my site.
Thank you very much.
What is this?
Is this a cell phone?
It's a cord to hang a cell phone from.
A cord?
Cord?
Here, take that board right there. Board?
You want to put it here?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm going to put this in here,
We have member colors.
Oh, wow!
That's so cute!
Amazing!
Six colors.
There are 6 colors.
It's nice.
Like the power.
Okay, let's get a clear case,
You can see it right here.
That's nice.
It's nice.
You should definitely get one of these.
It's so cute.
This string also comes in six different colors.
Wow!
The fastener has a logo on it, too.
That's right.
It's cute.
It's so cute.
After all, in this day and age, it is said that a cell phone should be hung from the wall.
I enjoy it.
I can challenge myself.
It's nice.
Please get one.
Please do.
And,
What?
It's so cute!
Do you think we should put it on?
Do you want to put it on?
Is it cute?
Do you like that one?
Do you like having it?
That's what I thought.
Red and yellow?
Stab.
Stick them together.
You stick them here.
Is that all there is to it?
I thought so.
It's cute.
You stick them in.
You stabbed this one, too.
Isn't this one different, too?
It's black.
It's really black.
It works on its own.
It can be used by itself.
You put this on too, right?
Sure.
The key that opens the key that opens the key that opens the key that opens the key, the hand clack clack clack clack clack,
You can carry it around with you,
Wouldn't it be better if you put this on your bag?
Not at all. So it's for decoration,
And to carry it around,
And for preservation.
Even when it's broken.
Even when they are broken.
Some people open them.
Yay!
Again,
It's connected again, everyone.
Look at this, everyone.
It makes you sleepy.It makes me sleepy.
It makes you sleepy.
It makes me sleepy.
I've never seen so many screens used up in 3 min.
I've never seen it.
Is the quality of the open key good?
It's good.
What do you think? This is the quality of the open key.
Have you seen it?
It's really good.
It looks good.
Picture quality is good.
Is it shaking?
It's shaking.
It looks like it's going to hit the target.
I'm sure.
Yes, it is. So, everyone.
Yes.
I'll be following Matsu-san's Twitter later.
Please check it sometime.
It won't be right after this.
Maybe.
When you come.
There's something else, isn't there?
Oh!
Oh, my God, there's that one.
That thing.
Can I say something?
Can I say it?
What is it?
You can guess.
It's something that comes out at the time of the anniversary.
Speaking of.
Oh!
T.
Are you sure?
There's also BOOM.
BOOM BOOM BOOM.
Do you want to get it?
Do you get it?
Will they think I'm a pussy?
I don't want a kitty either.
What?
What is it?
Huh?
The color will break it up.
The colors seem heavy.
Not at all in this area.
You say that about this area.
What is it? Mosaic?
Um...
I'm the best rear key.
Ha-ha-ha.
You forgot.
You forget, don't you?
Yes.
So, everyone.
Please check out the goods and other items.
Please check it out.
The goods for the anniversary are unique.
It's something you can't get anywhere else.
You have to get them.
And the request live?
Yes, there will be.
In August
Batten Music Day Unit and the Request Live that makes
will be held.
This is Friday, August 11.
The national holiday is
ZEPP Fukuoka.
And Sunday, August 20th will be
ZEPP Diver City.
Some of them will be performed by a band.
The band will also be performing.
Showing off.
We are going to showcase the band.
But, as I said before..,
The other day
the other day, we asked for setlist requests from the people of Thailand.
We asked for your setlist requests.
The results are in.
This is it,
We can see it now.
We had a lot of visitors.
We are very grateful.
There were many things to be thankful for.
By the way, the top one is my
survey.
Oh, it's on the website.
That's nice.
What kind of
What do you like?
I can see it all.You can see it all.
I can see it all.
It's like this.
What do you think?
This result.
You can see what I mean.
You know what I mean.
This is No. 1.
I'm sure.
I thought it would be in.
I thought it would be No. 1.
I got so many requests.
The number one song
The first song is the most popular, right?
Yes, there are a lot.
The number of requests on the first scale
I think that's the emotion.
emotion.
Yes, that's right.
The second scale, well..,
That's right.
Three.
Surprising.
3, 4. Surprising.
Indeed.
It is also surprising that this is 5.
I wonder if they should be in.
Surely.
Surprising.
By the way, if a member were to vote for three, what would they be?
Wait a minute, didn't you put this in earlier? Because I've already put it in.
I've already put it in.
Wow, I wonder what it is.
I wonder.
I wonder what kind of system it is. There are so many.
Do you want to do or see something?
Don't you want to see it? Of course you want to see.
Do you want to see it?
From the same perspective as the fans.
I want to see.
Wow, I want to see it.
They were doing the third season.
I'm torn.
I'm quite worried about this.
I'm quite worried about it. This.
I'm looking at what you guys did.
It's so fast. You're fast.
Well, everyone.
By the way, what did you choose for Sakura?
In my case,
Let's see,
My first choice is...
Invincible Venus.
Oh.
And my second choice is...
Ayoyo miya.
Oh!
Aiyorimiya.
Mr. Shirai's choice,
Hot Kanakana Tsuki Sokku.
Aah!
I thought that I would like to see
I see.
That's right.
You know, it bothers me. Really.
It bothers me.
And this, you know, including the formation of the band, right?
That's right.
That also plays a part, doesn't it?
That's true. In thinking about it.
Oh, that's right.
But when I look at what you have done..,
I want to be a dancer, although it's difficult for me.
Oh, sure.
Ai, I want to be in Meguri.
Meguri.
That's nice.
Wow, but a lot of them. Nice.
Impressions. It's good, isn't it?
Sure is.
Considering 70,000 units.
And considering the impressions, we got a special day.
Oh, that's good.
It's good.
It's strong.
That's strong.
That's nice.
I want to see BPM too.
That's cool. Definitely. I like it.
Let's do all the songs. I'm sure.
Sure. Sure.
I'm not talking about Equestrian. Sure.
I'm talking about a concert where you play all the songs over several days. That's for sure. Even if it takes a few days.
Over several days.Over a few days.
And Lira? But Lira already.
Invincible, Specialdy, BBB...
Liamoy...
I like it.
Wow.
I can be bothered.
Wow, but yeah.
Isn't it hard? I mean, I've seen a lot of live shows where they might be a band.
I don't know yet.
You're right.
That's great.
That's great. Everyone let me know you're on line.
Thank you very much.
Oh, I see. I put it in Megli.
Grown-ups are usually cool, too.
They'll be cool for a few days, too.
Everyone's so last-minute that they get mad at me.
They come in with a lot of ideas.
I'm glad. What kind of music is this too?
And of course, the music will be different in Tokyo and Fukuoka.
So this is also important.
So it's important to have the same music in Kuroda.
Important, important, important!
That's right.
I was wondering if you'd be there.
It's hot today, isn't it?
It's hot today. It was hot today.
It was hot today.
It was sunny today, wasn't it?
It wasn't. Fukuoka?
It was sunny in Fukuoka. Nice.
This questionnaire... how did you start supporting the Archangel?
No, no, no, there's a reason why I chose it.
You can choose? I saw it. I saw it. It's true. It's true.
I really like one of the reasons I started cheering for you.
I wonder where they went. I wonder where they went.
I'm already loving it so much.
I love it so much! I love it so much!
Oh, there it is!
The use of margarine in the MC...
Oh, that...
Yes, someone liked it.
Wow, that's rare.
That's rare. -Wow. How is that possible?
80%. It was actually the lowest.
Thank you very much.
It was the margarine that started it all.
It's a long and winding road.
Thank you very much.
But I'm surprised. It's nice to see you.
Yeah.
Some of you have been with us since the beginning.
Right?
There are quite a few.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad to hear that.
It's nice to see you.
That's a lot of people.
I didn't include anyone from the celebration festival in the celebration at all, is that okay?
Ha-ha-ha.
There it is. I have a reason.
There's a reason.
There's a trigger.
I've been asking too many questions.
The trigger...
I asked too much.
He's even more expensive.
Yes, there is.
Amazing!
Ha-ha-ha.
I wonder who came through Miyu Yanagi.
I wonder where she came from.
Ha-ha-ha.
You came through, right, Miyu?
You came via...
She came through you because of how you started, right?
Ah...
That's funny.
I'm asking how it all started, but the members are so cute.
Thank you.
There's Yoshiko Ueda, too.
There's also Miko Ueda. Thank you.
Great. I like her because I like her. I like her.
Oh...
Straight up.
Ha-ha-ha.
That's great!
This is so funny.
It's funny, isn't it?
Ha-ha-ha!
I'm so glad you guys write so much.
It's true.
I mean...
Go.
You know...
It's spread out, isn't it?
It's a big place
I'm so happy!Oh, I'm so happy!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure you'll all be comforted by this.
We'll decide on the requested songs for the show.
Yes.
Please look forward to it.
Please come and join us.
Please do.
Please do!
Widely
Here.
Yes, here
Right here.
We're only going to play two songs today.
We'll decide.
Well...
What should we do?
But I want to save one of them.
Don't tell anyone.
Sure.
Let's keep it a secret.
Don't tell anyone?
Yes, ma'am.
Don't tell the other one.
Mm-hmm.
Top.
Top tunes.
Uh...
What do we do now?
What do we do?
You know, we can decide here.
Yeah, I'm sure we'll do it.
But I'm sure you'll do it.
I'm sure we'll do it.
Wow, but it's two songs.
But, you know, I think we'll do 3, right?
You want to do it.
I do. I want to do it.
I want to do it.
Wow.
Ask them what they want to know. Sure.
I'm almost done. I'm not going to say one or two more.
I won't. I'm sure we'll do one or two.
What's good?
I thought 7th.
I'll settle for ninth.
What else do you have in mind?
We're just going to get picked?
Yeah.
Do we get to choose?
I'd like to.
It's a band, right?
If there's a band in it,
I'll do a special.
I'd love to do that.
It would be nice. And it's relatively high up.
It's a relatively high rank.
I like it.
Oh!
What?
Den
Oh!
It's good, isn't it?
Special Day.
Then let's do a special day.
We'll do it.
Where should we do it?
Should we do it at both places?
I don't know.
We will have a special day.
Yay!
We will do it.
Yes!
Great, great.
One more song?
One more song.
I'm torn, man.
I'm torn.
I'm so confused.
Wow.
Which one? Which one?
Well, I wonder what they're writing based on.
Ah.
Wow.
Eh, they're all good.
I'd love to do any of them.
Yeah, I'm sure you do.
I know you're gonna do the top ones.
I'll let you know today.
Yes, sir.
What will it be?
Don't hesitate. Don't get lost.
Well, because, you know, I'm a fan, and I'm a fan of the band sound system, but I've never heard it in a band sound system,
but I've never heard it with a band sound,
That's true.
But your songs are good.
Yeah, they are. Summery songs are good, too.Yes, it is. Summery songs are good, too.
Surely, if you're going to go to all this trouble.
A summery song.
I don't know where we can find a song like that.
But then again, isn't it Atsatsuka?
Yes, I guess so.
Sure, various. Anjohi.
That's cool. Like Anschocke.
That's cool.
Wow, wait, wait, wait. What do we do? Seriously.
Can you decide? I'll make a decision.
Can you decide?
Wow, you guys are amazing. They're looking at so many things.
Isn't Mirin pretty popular?
Maybe she is.
But popular?
I don't think so.
Ranking?
A little popular?
A little behind.
What?
They didn't say it was a reference.
They didn't call this one "Usako", did they?
That's right.
It's difficult, isn't it?
It's not easy.
It's difficult.
It's summer.
It's true.
Autumn and summer.
It's not the beginning of summer.
It was summer once.
Oh, no.
Wait a minute. What do you want?
What do you want?
But, you see, we know who theorizes about the 8th anniversary, don't we?
That's for sure.
When I think about it.
Let's put it aside, shall we? Then the summer.
Yes, I guess so.
Is it okay if I tell you?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
They're all...
I haven't heard.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Please.
Is this good?
I did it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Wow.
Ladies and gentlemen, potatoes po hatas po choute.
Oh, no.
No, what?
I really can't do this.
I can't choose.
I can't choose between third and fourth place.
Huh?
Oh, 3.
There's this 5th place.
What do you mean, fifth place?
Sixth?
How did you get sixth?
Sinkuru.
You're a fan of Kinaki.
They were expecting something.
L, right?
L. L.
L. I think I'll do it.
I'm not going to say "M" anymore because I'm going to do it.
M is for 7th place or so.
That's right.
What are you going to do? Do you want to do N?
Wait a minute, which N?
Oh, N.
You want to do N?
N. - What? What are you going to do?
We can decide. We don't want to do it right now.
I want to do this.
But don't you also want to do O?
O is good.
Oh, O.
V is good.
What about V?
I'd like to do V.
I want to do V.
I want to do it.
Not V.
Yes, it is.
Excel?
It's not eniscal.
He said it's not Eniscal.
Excel.
V is good, right?
V is good.V might be nice.
I'd like to do it.
Because everyone thinks it's inocial.
Sorry.
On the Excel.
That one is difficult.
There is no "V" music, is there?
No, there isn't.
It's a V.
Okay, let's go with V.
Isn't it summer?
It's summer.
It's like August, isn't it?
It's good, isn't it?
Let's go with that.
Let's do it.
Master by!
How about MASTER BY for the special date?
It's decided.
I'm looking forward to it.
No V. It's bad, isn't it?
V.
So,
BB.
I love special days.
Thank you very much.
So, Special Day and
MASTER BY will do.
Yes, we will.
Please come and see us.
If you want to see this, we have already decided to come.
If you want to see this, you've already decided to come.
This is not happening.
It's not someone who knows what he's doing.
It doesn't happen often.
Please come see us.
Please come to see me.
So, emergency live broadcast.
I hope you enjoyed it,
Did you enjoy it?
It was fun.
Thanks to An-chan in places.
I don't think my memory is like this,
I almost fell asleep.
But...,
June has come,
Starting this week, events and live performances will continue every week.
Events and live performances will continue every week from this week,
June, July, and August.
I hope to see you at the live concerts in June, July, and August.
Please come and see us.
We are looking forward to seeing you.
I will be in Paris in July,
I'll be in Paris in July, so we'll see what kind of live show we will have in Paris.
I am also looking forward to
I'm looking forward to it,
every week.
First of all, this week
Taiwan live with Dance Osawa this week,
and Hiroshima Flower Fest.
If you are coming to see us,
I hope we can have fun together.
Thank you very much.
Now, what do you have in store?
No?
No, I don't have anything. I have no announcements, so that's all I have to say.
We have a little extra time.
Oh, we've got eight minutes left.
Let's chat.
Ah, 7 minutes left.
Chat Yanken, I'm looking forward to a lot of things.
Thank you very much.
If you are looking forward to a lot of things.
Do you have an MVP without my permission?
I missed it.
I didn't get that many comments.
I'm going to play the song I just decided on at the request live show.
You guys, I don't understand a bit.
Oh, I'm sorry.
We'll do it at the request live.
We will do it at the request live.
It's August in August.
It's the day of music.
Yes.
We will do it here, please.
Please do it.
Do you want to read something in the chat room?
Yes, I do.
Miyu, please upload your work.
Sure thing.
Wow, Miyu.
If you look at it like this, it's kind of really amazing.
Everyone has black hair.
Indeed.
She's cute.It's cute.
It's cute.
Cute.
First time.
Scary, scary.
I'm scared. A little bit.
Will you do it?
I have to do it.
I'm a little scared.
There's a guy doing an ackee trick. On the screen.
Thank you.
Cute.
I got it.
It's cute.
Cute.
So cute.
Let's read the reasons for the two song requests at random, shall we?
I see.
This is the hardest part every time.
What was that? How do you see it?
What is it?
Who's in the special games.
Someone who plays special games.
I don't know. It's hard.
It's a little bit. How do you see it?
I'm sorry. It's difficult.
It's a little difficult.
I can only see the time of year and stuff. I don't know what to do.
I want to make it a little more close-up, don't I?
I'm sure. I want to make it up.
Can you make it up?
Up.
I want to make it wider.
The front.
Is it too long?
Yes, I do.
Cute. Cute.
Because it's cute?
Is it cute?
It says "kawaii" on it.
Kawa. I see. Because he's cute.
And she can't talk.
Can't talk. JIKI.
It's a form of "jiki".
Was it a Jiki?
Yes, it was. I can't listen to it or something.
This is another song that I haven't heard very often recently, so I'd like to see the members who are all swinging for cuteness.
So this is how you see it.
On this special day, I want a present because I'm a nerd.
What?
I have a present for you.
The song is cool. Special Day.
Eh~.
I can do it.
I'll see it when I press it. Wow, that's great.
What is it?
Is it different?
Did you send it?
Sent what?
What? Aren't you a specialist?
I'm a specialist, aren't I?
Yes, I'm a specialist.
Did you read it? Good, good, good.
Did you send it?
You sent it.
I can't help it.
I like Fishers. It's a cute worldview with a strong sense of duty,
Indeed, indeed, indeed.
I'm also very happy to hear Aichan's feast of memories, and it's a memorable song.
It's nice.
Yeah, it goes well with the band sound.
I hear that too. Yeah.
Yes, it goes well with the band sound. It's cool, I'm sure.
It's my favorite song. Oh!
Oh, seriously, this is the only way to do it.
I'm glad you guys are sending us stuff.
They're sending it to me.
Yeah, like this one.
Is it a must-have?
It's a must-buy.
Must-buy.
Must-Buy... it's a must-buy.
It's gonna be a blast.
Must bye... what did we do?
That English.
English?
Thank you.
It's the song I wanted to hear most with the band.
I could've seen it.
As for the merchandise, the towels are still in production.
I see.
The same pattern as those.
The same pattern.
The one I saw.
Yes, the one that says "Bappen" on it.
I see.
Pony pony.Poniponi.
Roger that.
I think everyone should have one of these.
Sure thing.
I agree.
That's right.
If you don't have one, tell me why you don't have it.
Why?
Please have it.
It's true, I don't sweat.
It's summer.
That's true.
You need it in the summer.
That's right.
You'll definitely need it in the summer.
And I think you can throw the towel around now.
I see.
It's also important to know where to spin the towel.
I think it's time to start spinning.
Not in the city.
Not on the street.
You'll get caught.
Yes, but not on the street.
No, but...
This way, right?
We're still selling them.
I see.
Is it selling?
It's selling.
It's selling, but...
It's selling well.
It's a popular design.
After a lot of use, they get a little stiff.
Yes, it does.
That's true.
After all, you change towels every day.
You can have as many as you want.
That's fine.
Can I split it with you?
So, if you could all use this current design...
by all means!
Please get it!
Please, please.
And Strop?
That's it.
I'll make my own original.
Yes.
This time.
What's that? This way?
This way?
This way? That way?
Make it your own.
It's so unique.
That's amazing.
It's in the order of the members' ages.
That's great.
Amazing.
It's true.
And it's so easy to use for everyday life!
Hey.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
I'm sleeping.
Anyone use the strop on their phone yet?
Yes, I am.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're behind, folks.
Late.
There was no hole.
Present for you.
Are you sure?
Take it off.
Yes, in the case.
You mind?
It's fine.
Are you okay?
If it's okay with Sora.
As far as Sora is concerned.
So it can be used on both iPhone and Android.
That's nice.
As long as you put a case on it.
Yes. Please get one.
Yes. And..,
8th anniversary T.
Limited edition.
T and
New member color.
New!
New? That's right,
Does that mean the 8th anniversary and the member's color are different items?
Is the 6th anniversary a different item from the 8th anniversary?
Yes, that's right.
There was a seventh idea, wasn't there?
There is no 7th idea.
There is the one for the Kyushu tour.
I see.
The member's color T, right?
That's nice.Nice.
You have to get it, people.
Please get it.
And this is also new.
New.
These are the costumes for the spring tour.
So, let's get it.
It's nice.
It's cute, everyone.
Please get it.
And..,
Rubber bum!
It's been a while since I've been rubber shopping.
I wonder if it came out on the 6th anniversary of the 6th anniversary of the 6th anniversary of the 6th anniversary of the 6th anniversary of the 6th anniversary of the 6th anniversary...
Glow? Did it come out on that 7th anniversary?
It's been a year. It's been a long time.
If you haven't got it yet. You can put it on your arm or your bag.
You can put it on your arm or on your bag.
It's twice off.
Two cuts.
Here's what we're planning on doing with the merchandise.
I hope you get all of them.
I hope you can get one of these.
Please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, check it out.
Please check it out!
That's all, I'm leaving. Thank you very much for watching.
See you again at the live and other events.
That's all for now, Patention's team.
Bye bye.